bocaexecutiverealty.com 2014-09-12

# 

> ###  Boca Executive Realty Online Privacy Policy
> 
> November 2007
> 
> Your privacy is important to us at Boca Executive Realty, LLC (“Boca Executive Realty”). Our online privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) describes the types of information we gather from those persons visiting the Internet Web site, [ www.bocaexecutiverealty.com](http://www.bocaexecutiverealty.com/ "Boca Raton Real Estate") (the “Site”) and how we use that information. By accessing this Site, you agree to be bound by the Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use this Site. Each time you use the Site, the current version of the Privacy Policy will apply. Accordingly, when you use the Site, you should check the date of this Policy (which appears at the top) and review any changes since the last version.
> 
> 1\. Use of Information Collected by Us   
>  Boca Executive Realty may collect two types of information from users of our Site: "personally identifiable information" (such as name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, etc.) and "aggregate information" (frequency of visits to the Site, search terms entered, Site pages most frequently accessed, IP address, browser type, etc.)   
>  We use this information in an effort to improve your experience on the Site and to communicate with you about products, services, surveys, promotions and contests. We may also use this information to make offers to you, to help us target specific products and services to you, and to help us develop and improve our Site and tailor our Site to your interests.   
>  2\. Collection of Personally Identifiable Information 
> 
> Boca Executive Realty only collects personally identifiable information that is voluntarily provided by users of the Site when users register with the Site (as “registered members”). For example, when you register on the Site, you may be required or requested to provide personally identifiable information such as your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, moving plans, etc.   
>  3\. Collection of Aggregate information  
>  Boca Executive Realty also collects aggregate information, which is non-personally identifiable/anonymous information about you, such frequency of visits to the Site, search terms entered, Site pages most frequently accessed, IP address, browser type, etc. Aggregate Information is used in a collective manner, and no single person can be identified by that compiled information. 
> 
> 4\. Sharing, Selling, and Trading Personally Identifiable Information Collected Online with Third Parties  
>  Boca Executive Realty may share or disclose personally identifiable information, such as name, address, company name, profession, moving plans, email address, or phone number, to unrelated third parties so these third parties can contact you for marketing and promotional purposes.   
>  Additionally, in the following circumstances we may share or transfer personal information to unrelated third parties: (i) to comply with a legal requirement, judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on Boca Executive Realty, (ii) to investigate a possible crime, such as fraud or identity theft; (iii) in connection with the sale, purchase, merger, reorganization, liquidation or dissolution of Boca Executive Realty; or (iv) when we believe it is appropriate to do so to protect the rights, property, or safety of Boca Executive Realty or other persons.   
>  5\. Sharing, Selling and Trading Aggregate Information Collected Online With Third Parties  
>  We may sell, share or trade compiled aggregate information with third parties. As stated earlier, no single person can be identified by such aggregate information.
> 
> 6\. Protection of Personal Information
> 
> We will protect your personal information with safeguards appropriate to the sensitivity of the information. 
> 
> 7\. Use of Cookies/Pixel Tags
> 
> Cookies are pieces of information which websites transfer to your computer’s web browser for storage on your computer’s hard drive. Boca Executive Realty uses cookies to measure activity on our Site, which allows us to improve navigation throughout our Site. In addition, cookies on the Site may contain information (such as an unique user ID), which tracks the pages of the Site you have visited. This information allows us to make updates to enhance your experience. Parts of the Site will not function if you do not have cookies enabled. You can set your browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If you turn off cookies or refuse them, though, you will not be able to use every portion of our Site. 
> 
> A pixel tag, also known as a clear GIF or web beacon, is an invisible tag placed on certain pages of our Site but not on your computer. When you access these pages, pixel tags generate a generic notice of that visit. They usually work in conjunction with cookies, registering when a particular computer visits a particular page. If you turn off cookies the pixel tag will simply detect an anonymous website visit.
> 
> 8\. Children and Privacy 
> 
> Boca Executive Realty is concerned about the safety of children when they use the Internet, and understands that children may not understand all the provisions of our Privacy Policy or make informed decisions about the choices that are made available to adult users of the Site. We encourage parents and guardians to spend time with their children online and to be familiar with the sites their children visit. Our Site is not directed to children under the age of 18. Additionally, we will never request personally identifiable information from anyone whom we know to be under the age of 13 without verifiable parental consent. If we become aware that a user is under the age of 13 and has registered without prior verifiable parental consent, we will remove his or her personally identifiable registration information from our files. 
> 
> 9\. Security
> 
> The security of your personal information is important to us and Boca Executive Realty is committed to handling your customer information carefully. We make reasonable efforts to follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personally identifiable information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personally identifiable information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. IN NO EVENT WILL BOCA EXECUTIVE REALTY OR ITS AFFILIATES OR ANY PARTY INVOLVED IN CREATING, PRODUCING OR DELIVERING THIS SITE BE LIABLE IN ANY MANNER WHATSOEVER FOR ANY INCIDENTAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, INDIRECT, SPECIAL OR PUNITIVE DAMAGES ARISING OUT OF YOUR ACCESS, USE OR INABILITY TO USE THIS SITE, OR IN CONNECTION WITH ANY FAILURE OR PERFORMANCE, ERROR, OMISSION, INTERRUPTION, DEFECT, DELAY IN OPERATION OR TRANSMISSION, COMPUTER VIRUS OR LINE OR SYSTEM FAILURE (INCLUDING LOSS PROFITS, LOSS OF BUSINESS OR DATA, BUSINESS INTERRUPTION, AND DAMAGES THAT RESULT FROM INACCURACY OF THE INFORMATION OR INCONVENIENCE, DELAY, OR LOSS OF THE USE OF THE SITE). THE FOREGOING LIMITATIONS APPLY WHETHER THE ALLEGED LIABILITY IS BASED ON CONTRACT, TORT, NEGLIGENCE STRICT LIABILITY OR ANY OTHER BASIS, EVEN IF BOCA EXECUTIVE REALTY OR ITS AFFILIATES OR ANY OTHER PARTY HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. 
> 
> 10\. Links to Other Websites
> 
> This Site may contain links to websites operated by other people or companies. Those websites may have their own privacy policy or no privacy policy at all. Boca Executive Realty does not have any responsibility for those websites, and we provide the links solely for the convenience of our visitors. 
> 
> 11\. Business Transfers 
> 
> In the event that Boca Executive Realty sells substantially all of its assets, or one of its units are acquired, personally identifiable information of visitors to the Site and aggregate information will likely be one of the transferred assets. 
> 
> 12\. Changes to this Policy   
>  Boca Executive Realty reserves the right to update or modify this Policy, at any time and without prior notice, by posting the revised version of this Policy on our Site.  
>  13\. Corrections/Information Removal/Opt-Out
> 
> If your name, e-mail or postal address, telephone number or other personally identifiable information changes, you may update, correct or omit the relevant information by making the change(s) by logging in with your registration information or by contacting us through the portion of our site labeled “contact us.”  
>  If you prefer not to receive marketing e-mails from Boca Executive Realty, please let us know by (a) sending us an e-mail at privacy@bocaexecutiverealty.com, (b) by following the unsubscribe instructions located at the end of any marketing e-mail you receive from us or (c) by phoning us at 800-700-9806 or 561-544-3810. If you prefer not to receive marketing mail via the mail carrier, please let us know by sending a request to Boca Executive Realty, LLC, 4800 N. Federal Hwy., Suite A105, Boca Raton, Florida 33431. Please be sure to include in any e-mail or postal mail, your full name, e-mail address, postal address, and any message. Please note that such requests may take up to ten (10) days to become effective.   
>  If you do not wish to have personal information collected at our Sites shared with third-party organizations (unrelated to Boca Executive Realty) for their marketing or promotional purposes, you can have your name placed on a "do-not-share" list (in which case, such personal information will not be shared with third parties unrelated to Boca Executive Realty) by sending a request to: Boca Executive Realty, LLC, 4800 N. Federal Hwy., Suite A105, Boca Raton, Florida 33431. In addition, you may call us to become part of the "do-not-share" list at 1-800-700-9806   
>  14\. Contact Us
> 
> If you have questions regarding this Privacy Policy or the information collection and dissemination practices of this Site, please contact us at:
> 
> E-mail: privacy@bocaexecutiverealty.com  
>  Phone: 561-544-3810  
>  Fax: 561-423-5956  
>  Toll Free: 800-700-9806  
>  Mail: Boca Executive Realty, LLC  
>  4800 N. Federal Hwy.  
>  Suite A105  
>  Boca Raton, FL 33431
> 
>   
> 

© Copyright 2005-2014, Boca Executive Realty, LLC the leader in luxury home sales in Florida. Find [Boca Executive Realty](https://plus.google.com/100773485285291991024) and [Zev Freidus](https://plus.google.com/116815584220578552758?rel=author) on Google+
